

# CONTACT

- +998995640297
- ≤ sarvar9818sh@gmail.com
- Tashkent
- ♠ GitHub
- @SARVAR0297
- Achievements

## **EDUCATION**

Sep 2017 - July 2021

# TASHKENT UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

• Computer engineering

# SKILLS

- PHP
- OPP
- MVC
- PSR
- Laravel
- MySql
- React is
- JavaScript
- REST API
- HTML and CSS
- Firebase
- Git

# **SARVAR SHOMURODOV**

# BACKEND DEVELOPER

### **PROFILE**

Aspiring Junior PHP Backend Developer with 2+ years of experience in Laravel Framework. Skilled in utilizing PHP, Laravel Framework, MVC, and RestAPI. Eager to apply expertise and learn new technologies in a collaborative team environment.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Astrum IT Academy** Fullstack Developer

Aug 2021 - Sep 2022

### **Online Shop**

A site that sells a variety of products. It has a convenient interface. Admin page to add products to the site and manage them. I used Laravel Breeze Authentication to register site users. I did the backend in Laravel and the design in Blade. I have created a section for the list of discounted products, and pagination in Laravel so that no more than 20 products are displayed on one page. The data is stored in a MySql database. I used migrations to manipulate the database state. Eloquent ORM was used to, manipulate get data, process and retrieve to an end user.

• Project link: https://github.com/SarvarShomurodov/Online\_shop\_laravel

### **Termiz Suv**

This project is a full-stack web app. I used Laravel for the backend and Blade for the design.CRUD system was introduced to upload and manage the necessary documents on the backend side. Spatie Role permission to manage the main roles on the app. The data is stored in a MySql database. I used migrations to manipulate the database state. I used the Laravel UI authentication library to register the users. Addons like JavaScript and Ajax are used to create complex design elements and add interactivity.

Project link: https://github.com/SarvarShomurodov/uzsuv

#### IMRS May 2021 - Present

#### Fullstack Developer

 I work as a php programmer at IMRS company. In this company, economic projects are implemented. I create websites for these projects. For example http://lmis.imrs.uz/

#### **Astrum IT Academy**

Oct 2021 - May 2024

**Fullstack Mentor** 

 Mentored and supported over 600 students, empowering them with the skills and knowledge needed to proficiently write code in the PHP programming language. Most of my students are currently working as full-stack developers in IT companies.

### LANGUAGES

- Uzbek (Native)
- Russian (A2)
- English (B1)